I bring you a tip.
The crown prince, Second Prince Albert,
plans to lead
a coup tonight...
and force His Majesty
to abdicate the throne.
Born Blessed, So I'll Obtain Ultimate Power
Episode 12
Nobility
Albert?
No, wait a minute.
You said your name was Olivia?
How do you know this?
I am the daughter of Coil, a member of
former First Prince Gilbert's household.
Coil, his butler?
You were born into the household?
Yes.
Born into a household...
That refers to a child born between
two servants of a prince's house.
Since that's the environment
they grow up in,
it's easy for them to swear
absolute loyalty to that prince.
I know all about how you managed
to spare the First Prince's life.
And yet, that man...
I see. At the time, my
father was probably...
So I swore revenge and approached him...
with this body my parents gave me.
And then I heard it.
Before the official proclamation
of his disinheritance,
while he was still the crown prince,
he would mobilize soldiers and
take control of the palace.
What does Albert intend
to do to His Majesty?
Force him to abdicate and become
an emperor emeritus, he said.
I beg of you!
My body, my very life...
They are yours to use as you see fit!
Just, please... stop Crown Prince Albert!
Please...
All right.
What did you do at Gilbert's house?
I-I was an apprentice
butler under my father.
Then you'll do that here, too.
You'll be paid the same
as you were there.
From tomorrow on, you don't
need to do anything special.
Why... would you treat me so well?
When you lost your master,
you tried to avenge him.
I merely acknowledged your loyalty
in serving your master to the
end, even after his death.
How remarkable you are...
I humbly offer myself in your service!
Dark
Master?
I'm going out for a bit.
A-All right! Um... A carriage, then?
No. I'll go alone.
Huh?
B-But it's so late...
Gigi.
We shall await your return, Master.
Right.
Please be safe.
If Albert intends to use
his right of command,
there's only one force he could lead.
It's stationed at the Ministry
of Military Affairs.
A thousand men.
Since they're permanently stationed,
they've been trained to obey the orders
of the superior officer in command
without a second thought.
Hear me!
Are you familiar with the
saying, "Even water can rot"?
Water that forgets to flow and
stays in one place too long
eventually stagnates and becomes
a home for all manner of vermin.
The same can be said of a nation!
His Majesty has forgotten
to flow for far too long,
and now, vermin swarm around him in the
form of disloyal, treacherous retainers,
trying to rot this country
from the inside!
Justice sides with me!
I will return the empire you love to
the hands in which it was meant to be!
Please hold, Brother!
Ah, Noah. What brings
you here at this hour?
Please refrain from doing
anything senseless!
There is still time!
Who told you?
That doesn't matter!
Brother, if you take this step, you
will bring about your own ruin!
What of it?!
I refuse to die while sitting
around doing nothing!
Die?
You haven't read His Majesty's edict
regarding your disinheritance?
You don't know the agony
His Majesty felt writing that?!
No matter what you may have done,
he did not disclose it publicly.
His Majesty wants you to live!
He agonized over a way to
allow you to keep your life!
So I should be content with
just being a prince?!
Thirty-five years...
I waited thirty-five years!
I believed that I would sit
on that throne one day...
that I would rule this empire!
And this is what I get?!
His Majesty seems to value his own
life above all in his old age.
If he insists on clinging
pathetically to the throne,
I will oust him with military might,
as is befitting of a military nation.
Content with just being a prince?
From the perspective
of the common folk,
as well as my own,
the status of prince is most noble.
They do what they think is best,
and have the power to act in
the interests of the people.
A prince is born blessed.
But since Albert was
once the crown prince,
being reduced to that status
must be akin to death.
This vast difference
in values must mean...
You insist on trying to stop me?
Yes.
I see.
Well, that's the kind of
younger brother you are.
Apprehend Noah!
He's a traitor!
A thousand of them.
They still follow orders faithfully, even
if ordered to attack a prince.
They are indeed well-trained.
All the more reason I can't
involve them in this!
Come!
Master.
Summon the power you
desire by its true name.
The power... I desire...
Go, Luthier!
No...
Bahamut!
Flowing water allows no contamination.
A breath of wind becomes the
eyes and ears that know all.
The earth is the foundation to
support the feet that move forward.
And flame...
manifests here as the
power to burn all to ash!
Wh-What is that?!
That's enough.
Don't kill any soldiers.
It's over, Brother.
You'll kill me? You? You?!
No. I will not take your life.
His Majesty would most certainly be sad
if one of his sons killed another.
So...
Poison?!
Precisely.
I will not kill you myself,
but I will not stop you
from killing yourself.
Be serious! Who do you think you are?!
Have you considered?
If I kill you, then you and all
your family and subordinates
will be executed as traitors.
But if you kill yourself now,
the story will be that you led
a force to attempt mutiny,
but stopped at the last moment
and killed yourself instead.
You cannot erase this act from existence.
But you can still spare your
family and subordinates,
and your eldest son can
still succeed you...
The choice is yours, Brother.
Who would fall for such nonsense?!
Foster! Howard!
Apprehend this boy!
It's not over yet.
I'll kill that dotard and
take the throne if I must—
Wh-What are you doing?!
We can no longer follow you.
Even under these
circumstances, Prince Noah
showed consideration for your
family and subordinates.
Yet this is what you're doing?!
Are you mad?! I'm telling you
not to entertain his nonsense!
Silence!
Do you...
Do you remember the 120 people
you sacrificed to the miasma
when you lifted the seal on
Leviathan all those years ago?!
So that's what...
My older brother was one of them!
My friend from childhood, too!
My father was among them, as well.
I can't follow you any longer!
You can't expect me to!
Nonsense! I am the crown prince!
Your lives belong to m—
Prince Noah, it seems the
crown prince regrets his actions
and has chosen to commit suicide.
What?!
Very well.
Olivia.
Yes.
Thank you.
Y-You can't be serious!
Have you forgotten your debt
to me for taking you in?!
S-Stop...
Damn... you all...
Who do you... think I...
Thirty-five years...
I waited thirty-five years.
I believed that I would sit
on that throne one day...
that I would rule this empire.
Brother...
Prince Noah.
Tragically, Prince Albert, the man
who led us, has committed suicide.
His treacherous ambitions led him
to take command of our army,
but he realized the gravity of his
crime and deeply regretted it.
In his last moments, he begged that
his bereaved family be shown mercy.
Yes. My brother attempted a coup,
but due to a tip from a
loyal household member
and the bravery of his retainers in
risking their lives to stop him,
he got no farther than taking
command of some soldiers.
Therefore, under imperial law,
the informant and retainers
will be rewarded,
and other household members
will be overlooked.
I will encourage His Majesty to have
my brother's eldest son succeed him.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Name: Noah Ararat, Thirteenth Imperial Prince
Sex: Male
Title: Minister-Prince of Justice
Level: 3
HP: E+E
Fire: F+A
MP: F+E
Water: E+S
Strength: E+E
Wind: F+F
Stamina: F+E
Earth: F+F
Intelligence: F+E
Light: F+C
Spirit: F+E
Dark: F+F
Speed: F+E
Dexterity: F+E
Luck: F+E
My basic abilities went way up.
These two must be very strong.
Albert had subordinates
this talented turn on him?
People really are treasures.
But since he didn't appreciate that,
his coup was doomed to fail either way.
So this is where you've been.
Just a moment ago, this box reacted.
Perhaps Noah's magic sword
has begun to awaken.
Given Prince Noah's talent,
I can believe it.
So... what happened?
After receiving word around the same
time we did, Noah rushed to the scene.
And the crown prince...
took his own life with poison.
I see.
Leave me alone for a while.
Noah, even at a time like
this, you are remarkable.
And so...
Gilbert Ararat
and Albert Ararat,
the two princes who attempted to murder
the emperor and take his throne,
disappeared from this world.
As a result,
the Meeres Empire saw the beginning of a
new era of peace like none before.
Wow! That's amazing!
And that prince was around the
same age as you, right, Sister?
And yet he... That's amazing!
And then? What happened next?
I know not.
Huh?
Because this story...
Three Years Later
Nishil, Capital of Almeria
Look at this, Head Maid!
It's from Evelyn!
Oh, so it is.
Let's take our time reading it later.
We'll never finish if we
don't work efficiently.
Prince Noah is amazing.
There's still more?!
He's more popular than ever.
Still, this is way too much!
They're for both his fifteenth birthday
Right?
and his relocation to Almeria
to officially rule as its lord.
There are still two more rooms' worth.
Really? He gets more
and more every year...
Well, he's Prince Noah, after all.
That just shows how many
people he has saved,
and how many people want
to be of use to him.
Our master is amazing, isn't he?
Yes, he truly is.
Well, if you would finish up here.
Sure!
Your skill is as impressive as ever.
Audrey.
What would you like to do for breakfast?
I'll have it here.
Very well.
Zoey.
Of course.
Here you are.
Thank you.
It's just about time.
Yes.
My fifteenth birthday, when
I am stripped of my surname.
How I have long waited for the day!
But you'll be losing your surname.
That makes me happy.
Because this means I finally,
officially become your wife!
Don't be so impatient.
Either way, I have no intention
of giving the one I have welcomed
over my threshold to anyone else.
Of course.
I was talking to the emperor,
and it sounds like one of those
three will be next in line.
The fourth prince, Henry...
The eighth prince, Oscar...
But the one he's hoping
for is... that one.
Take care.
I think I'll go ahead and
bet it all on that boy.
Take care, Prince Noah.
Thank you.
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Becky Cottrill
Edgar Cruz
Gabriella Alabanza
S Bilyeu
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Becky Cottrill
Edgar Cruz
Gabriella Alabanza
S Bilyeu